六月六日
敬请关注
Stay tuned.
我们周末为你们送上最热门的歌曲
We have all the greatest hits coming at you all weekend.
-首先    -来吧  我们走
-First up--    -Come on, let's go, let's go!
走走走
Go, go, go, go!
所有人都趴下
Everybody on the fucking floor!
趴地下
Keep your head fucking down!
趴下
Get down!
打开金库  快去
Fucking vault's open, let's go for it.
快点
Now!
快走
Let's go, let's go.
快点走
Come on, let's go.
来吧  干掉他
Come on, let's get him.
你没事吧  操
Are you okay? Fuck!
-你还好吗    -我说不要去金库
-You all right?    -I said no vault!
该死的现金  就这样堆着
Look at all this fucking cash! A fucking stash!
你最好快点
You better hurry!
我刚中枪  我说不要去金库
I just got shot. I said no vault.
-钱就这样堆着    -混蛋
-The fucking money is right here!    -Fuck you!
警察要来了
The cops are coming.
-现金就这样堆着    -你妈的
-Look at all this cash on here.    -Fuck you!
快点
Let's go!
快走  你这个胆小鬼
Fucking let's go, you crybaby!
操  快点
Fuck! In a minute!
-快走    -走吧
-Go, go, go!    -Let's go, let's go, let's go.
-快走    -操  警察
-Go, go, go, go!    -Fuck! It's the cops!
-该死  不要警察    -你说什么
-Shit! No, not the cops.    -Are you fucking kidding me?
你不该在金库里浪费时间
You shouldn't have wasted time in the vault!
我们得走了  走吧
We gotta move. Let's go.
-把枪放下    -来不及了
-Put the gun down!    -We don't have time!
-妈的    -操
-Fuck it!    -Fuck!
在克鲁塞斯和教堂街口有警察中枪  叫救护车
We have a cop down at Cruces and Church. Send a bus!
一名嫌疑人仍在此街区  徒步  有武器
One suspect still in the area. On foot, heavily armed.
奈特  你他妈要去哪
Knight, where the fuck you going?
我们需要等待后援
We need to wait for backup.
请帮帮我
Help me, please.
马上叫救护车过来
Get a bus out here now.
这些自杀性神风特攻队混蛋  注定要失败
These are kamikaze, burn-out, born-to-lose motherfuckers.
谢谢你的专业建议
Thanks for your expertise.
枪击  枪击
Shots fired. Shots fired.
我们需要支援  马上  枪击
We need backup. Right now! Shots fired!
下车  婊子
Move, bitch!
快点
Move!
-放下枪    -滚开
-Drop it!    -Fuck off!
她车里还有个小孩  放下枪
She's got a fucking baby in the car, man! Drop the gun!
滚开  我他妈要杀了你  滚开
Fuck off! I will fucking kill you. Fuck off!
放下枪  冷静点  你会没事的
Drop it! Calm down, you're gonna be fine. You're gonna be okay.
-我会杀了她    -你会没事的
-I'll fucking kill her.    -You're gonna be fine.
-请放下枪    -给我滚开
-Drop the gun, please.    -Get the fuck out of here.
-把枪放下    -给我一架直升机
-Just put it down.    -Get me a goddamn helicopter.
-放下枪  想一想    -我会杀了她
-Put it down. Think about it!    -I'll fucking kill her!
-不    -扔掉枪
-No!    -Drop it!
-不  滚蛋    -把枪放下
-No. Fuck off.    -Drop the gun.
扔掉枪  老头
Drop it, old man.
扔掉枪  你这个老混蛋
Put the gun down, you old fuck.
操
Fuck.
内务部将进行审查  你知道该怎么做
Internal Affairs will conduct the review. You know the drill.
谢谢
Thank you.
怎样  在哪里
What and where?
这个人死了  另一人在里面
This one's dead, the other one's inside.
嘿
Hey.
你好  先生
Hello, sir.
先生  你能听到我说话吗
Sir, can you hear me?
他还没死
Is he alive?
我什么都没听到  一定是风大
I don't hear anything. Must be the wind.
带路吧
Lead the way.
里面那个家伙浑身是洞  你进去就知道
It's the guy all shot up inside, you can't miss him.
警官  下面交给我吧  谢谢你
Officer, I can take it from here. Thank you.
警官  你能听到我说话吗
Sir, can you hear me?
是吗  好的
Yeah? All right.
好的
Okay.
操
Oh, fuck!
-准备救护    -他撑不过去的
-Prep the bus.    -He's not gonna make it.
-噢    -来吧
-Oh.    -Come on.
来吧
Come on!
操  什么  你他妈在干什么
Oh, fuck! What? What the fuck are you doing?
-帮忙    -操  德兹
-Help.    -Fuck, Dezi!
-天哪    -来吧
-Oh, my God!    -Come on.
你们两个小年轻能够当救护员
Are you two fucking old enough to be EMTs?
脉搏是每分钟五十次
The pulse is, 50 bpm.
-肾动脉有破口    -准备手术
-The renal artery nicked.    -Prep for surgery.
先生  睁开眼睛  你能告诉我你的名字吗
Sir, eyes open. Will you be able to tell me your name?
告诉我你的名字  先生
Tell me your name. Sir? Sir?
好的  请让一让  我们要过去了
Okay. Make a hole, make a hole. We're coming through.
叫创伤外科医生来  布拉德利在哪
Get the trauma surgeon in. Where is Bradley? Get me...
你没事吧
You okay?
给我一根烟
Can I bum a cig?
《警探奈特3：独立》
噢
Oh.
你是怎么找到的
How did you find it?
她在哪里
Oh, where is she?
你是警探  你来告诉我
You're the detective, you tell me.
对
You're right.
曾几何时
Once upon a time--
曾几何时  我的丈夫
Once upon a time, I had a husband
根本不在乎我的感受和时间
who didn't give a shit about my feelings or my time.
我想和我女儿谈谈
I just want to talk to my daughter.
她是个成年人
She's an adult.
如果她不想  她可以不跟你说话
She doesn't have to talk to you if she doesn't want to.
我已经改变很多了
I'm better than ever, hell.
她不想和你说话
She doesn't want to talk to you.
她给我最后一条短信是  “别烦我”
Her last text was two words, "bite me."
我是想道歉
I'm trying to apologize.
这是什么
What's that?
看起来像什么
What does it look like?
她不是小孩了
She isn't a child.
她永远是我的孩子
She'll always be my kid.
你留下这只熊  我会确保她收到
Just-- you leave the bear. I'll make sure she gets it.
你继续跟我说特克斯和凯科斯群岛的事
So, you were telling me about Turks and Caicos.
不用理他
Hey, don't worry about him.
如果说他有什么擅长的  那就是隐形
If there's one thing that he's good at, it's leaving.
谢谢大家
Thanks everyone.
“走出笼罩我的黑夜”
"Out of the night that covers me
“眼前黑暗层层无底”
"Black as the pit from pole to pole
“感谢上帝曾赐予我”
"I thank whatever God may be
“那不可征服的灵魂”
"For my unconquerable soul
“就算处境紧急危难”
"In the fell clutch of circumstance
“既不畏缩也不惊叫”
"I have not winced or cried aloud
“任凭命运百般作弄”
"Under the bludgeonings of chance
“满头鲜血誓不低头”
"My head is bloody, but unbowed
“在这愤怒和阴森地”
"Beyond this place of wrath and shade
“还有无尽岁月威胁”
"And yet the menace of years
“可是我将毫不畏惧”
"Finds, and shall find me, unafraid
“大门宽窄并不要紧”
"It matters not how strait the gate
“不管如何受到惩罚”
"How charged with punishments the scroll
“我是我命运的主人”
"I am the master of my fate
“我是我灵魂的主宰”
"And I am the captain of my soul."
致丽贝卡·弗拉纳根警官和埃德加·科尔特斯警官
Ahem. To Officer Rebecca Flanagan and Officer Edgar Cortez.
好警察永远不会死
Good cops never die,
只会上升到天堂警察局
they just get promoted to the precinct in the sky.
安息吧
Rest in power.
致弗拉纳根警官和科尔特斯警官
To Officer Flanagan and Officer Cortez.
同意  下一轮我请
Hear, hear. Next round is on me.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
两罐百威啤酒
Two Budweisers.
我不能喝酒
I don't think I can drink.
给你  小子  六美元整
Here you go, kid. Six bucks even.
混蛋  他刚刚救了一条命
Hey, asshole. The man just saved a life.
他应得免费啤酒
He's earned a free one.
我讨厌这个地方
I hate this place.
这里还不错
It has its charms.
-十五美元    -你刚说六美元
-Fifteen bucks.    -You said six.
龙舌兰酒十五美元
Well, the tequila is 15.
什么龙舌兰酒
What tequila?
-我没看到    -随便
-I don't see any tequila?    -Whatever.
不要喝我的酒
Don't roofie my drink.
队长要我整周都在来回扫荡
Captain wants me pulling swing all week.
通知联盟
Tell the union.
-应该的    -要知道
-I should.    -You know,
这个时候这里有很多蠢人
there are too many stupid people around here at this time
在做傻事
doing stupid things.
不管万圣节和圣诞节  都没有国庆日重要
Hey, give me the Fourth over Halloween and Christmas any day.
几个小孩在放烟花
A couple of kids shooting some fireworks?
这没什么大不了的
No biggie for me.
这些烟花点燃了特斯拉的每一个警报
You know, those fireworks set off every single alarm in Teslas,
从这里到阿纳海姆的每一栋建筑
every single building, from here to Anaheim.
这让我很想念纽约
It actually makes me miss New York.
此外还得应付一些狗屁电话
And you're gonna have to deal with some bullshit phone calls.
嘿  小帅哥
Yo, Justin Bieber!
你这是在偷听
You eavesdropping right now?
是啊  被抓个正着  我叫德兹
Yeah, I'm busted. My name is Dezi. I--
给我滚蛋
Don't give a fuck.
这里是警察酒吧
This is a cop bar.
那不是警徽  对吧
That's not a badge, is it?
救护员
EMT?
你认为这个也可以
You think that means something?
是的
Yeah, so...
我得救你们的小命
I just have to save your sorry asses,
却不能来这里喝啤酒
but I can't have a beer with you?
笨蛋  怪不得当不上医生
Too thick to make it as a doctor.
听着  我很尊重
Look, I've got a lot of respect
那些警察兄弟  对吧
for my blue-blooded brothers, right?
我妈妈曾经是一名警卫
My mother was a guard.
你妈妈是一名警卫
So, your mother was a guard?
你在吹牛吧
And you're bragging about that?
警卫  就像美籍爱尔兰人
Guards. They're like the Irish us.
对了  你是爱尔兰人
Oh, yeah. Are you Irish?
我听说爱尔兰女孩很随和
I hear that Irish girls are very easy.
你妈妈怎么样
How is your mother?
你一定是脑子进水了  竟敢这样站在我面前
You must have shit for brains to step in front of me like this.
-好的    -你得走了
-Okay.    -You're gonna have to go.
我以为这里是自由的国度
Well, I thought this was the land of the free.
-不适合你    -对
-It ain't for you.    -Yeah.
好吧  我要喝完啤酒  谢谢
All right. I'll think I'll finish my beer. Thank you.
你必须离开
You have to go.
太好了  有一根大棒
Oh, great. Yeah, there's a baseball bat.
-给我滚出去    -好
-Get the fuck out of here.    -Okay.
什么  垒球比赛
What is this, like a softball league?
你得走了  老兄
You'll have to go, dude.
怎么样  你想玩  给我报名  我很乐意
What's going on here? You wanna go? Sign me up, I'm down.
把他妈的球棒给我
Give me the fucking baseball bat.
来  我们走吧
Come on, let's go.
怎么了  德兹
What the fuck, Dez?
我爱这个国家  我喜欢
I love this country. I love it.
走吧
Let's go.
谁去叫警察
Someone call the police.
脑震荡
Concussion?
不  只是脑瓜蠢
No, you're just stupid.
你干嘛要住在这个鬼地方
Why do you live in this shithole?
你给我找个便宜点的地方  我就搬去那
Well, you find me a cheaper place and I'll live there.
-要请假吗    -呃
-Any breaks?    -Pssh.
不
Nah.
糟了  五十分钟后要值班
Shit. We're on deck in 50.
噢  五十分钟后要值班
Oh, "we're on deck in 50."
口音怎么样
You like my accent?
和你看来一样好
About as good as you look.
-你不必走  不不不    -德兹
-You don't gotta go. No, no, no, no.    -Dezi...
这样可不行
This is the worst idea.
你别想太多了
You think too much.
你干嘛要在警察酒吧跟人打架
Why the hell did you start a fight in a cop bar?
他们不会让我们再进去酒吧
They're never gonna let us back in there.
我想知道为什么
I want an answer.
也许我差点就成为其中一个
Maybe 'cause I almost was one.
一个什么
One of what?
我一直想当警察
I always wanted to be a cop.
-胡说    -不撒谎
-Bullshit.    -No lie.
差点伤了我爸爸的心
Nearly broke my dad's heart.
不是个遵纪守法的公民
Not exactly a law-abiding citizen.
发生了什么事
And what happened?
噢  我
Oh... I...
我都没能通过部门面试
didn't exactly make it through the department interview.
他们说我的道德指针是歪的
Yeah, they said my moral compass was skewed, and what--
是吗
You?
是的  差不多这样
Yeah, I was this close, but...
是啊  我还是想做点好事
Yeah, I still wanted to do some good, you know.
救护员人生  宝贝
EMT life, baby.
不管怎样  可能比那些混蛋做得更好
Probably doing more good than those assholes, anyway.
大部分警察都是好警察
There are some good cops, like, most are good.
是吗  那你得给我介绍一个
Oh, yeah? Well, you'll have to introduce me to one.
也许吧
Maybe.
你认为我先挑起打架
I, think I started that fight.
首先  打架不是我挑起的
Well, first of all, I didn't start the fight.
好的
Okay.
我是在自卫  这区别很大
I was defending myself, which is a big difference.
好的
Sure.
我不知道  我只是想看看
I don't know, I guess I just wanted to see
洛杉矶警察到底有多强硬
how tough the LAPD really was, you know?
你真是疯了
You're crazy.
你真可爱
Oh, and you're adorable.
别这样叫我  永远不要
Don't call me that. Ever.
是  小姐
Yes, ma'am.
这是一次性的事情
This was a one-time thing.
好吧  这是一次性的事情
Oh, okay. It's a one-time thing
然后就变成了两次性的事情
and then it's a-- until it's a two-time thing.
然后是三次性的事情
And then it's a three-time thing, okay?
然后是四次性的事情
And then it's a four-time thing.
你觉得你很有魅力
You think you're so charming.
注射纳洛酮
Get the Narcan.
凯尔推了你
Did Kyle shove you?
我怎么说的
What did I say?
如果有人推你  你就揍他
If someone shoves you, you punch 'em.
如果他们拔刀  你就拔枪
If they pull a knife, you pull a gun.
如果他们带坦克  就给我打电话
If they bring a tank, call me. All right?
凯尔  过来
Kyle. Get over here.
起来
Get up.
你又在推他了
You've been pushing him around again.
米尔顿  你知道该怎么做
Milton, you know what to do.
继续
Go on.
握握手
Shake hands.
都好吗  走吧
All good? Go on.
我跟你说过不要无精打采
What did I say to you about slouching?
别太紧绷  得撑一个月
Easy on the spread, it has to last a month.
如果你妈妈看到了这个世界
You know, your mother would turn in her grave
她会在坟墓里翻脸
if she saw the world now.
这不是曾经的国家
This isn't the country it once was.
小小的奇迹  是我们所能期待的
Small miracles, that's all we can hope for.
长滩的所有帮派
You know, every gang in Long Beach
都想染指那些孩子
is trying to get their hands on those kids.
我们给他们提供食物  请家教
We feed them, get tutors for them.
这个庇护所  是一种遗产
This shelter? It's a legacy.
只要保持开放  传承就会持续下去
As long as it stays open, her memory will last.
妈妈会为你感到骄傲
Mom would be proud of you, Dad.
好吧  骄傲不是奢侈品  我负担得起
Yeah, well, pride isn't a luxury I-- I can afford, you know.
我用尽了所有力气才让这里的灯亮着
Takes all my strength to keep the lights on here.
我们被撤资了
We've been defunded.
是啊  削减预算
Yeah. Budget cuts.
他们就是这样说的  因为去年的骚乱
That's what they say, because of the riots last year.
政府不理解
The state doesn't get it, you know.
拯救孩子  就能拯救未来
Save a kid, you save the future.
总之  我得去谈正事了
Anyway, I got to get to business.
要不要我告诉他们青年中心关门了
Do you want me to tell the kids the youth center's closed?
-不  是我邀请他们来    -呃哼
-No, no, no. I invited them.    -Ahem.
他们将以创造性的方式帮助保持灯亮着
They're gonna help with creative ways to keep the lights on.
生命中的一切都是为了这一刻
Everything in your life has been leading up to this moment.
有关部门认为
It's the opinion of the department
为什么有人进入执法部门
that why someone enters law enforcement
与他们每天所做的工作同样重要
is as important as the work they do on a daily basis.
我为什么想当警察
Why do I wanna be a cop?
我喜欢甜甜圈
I like donuts.
枪战
Gunfights.
-汽车追逐    -好的
-Car chases.    -Okay, okay.
这不是你第一次评估
This isn't your first time, ain't it?
对
That's right.
这是为了安全考虑
But this is a safe space.
在纽约之后给你的第二次机会
You were given a second chance after New York,
我们要确保你不会重蹈牛仔的老路
and we need to make sure you don't slip into your old cowboy ways.
我不能告诉你的队长
I can't tell your captain
你何时可以安全地回到工作
that you're safe to go back in the streets
除非你不会对自己或他人构成危险
unless we know you're not a danger to yourself or others,
这是底线
that's bottom line.
听着  我做了口供
Look, I gave my statement.
这次射击完全没问题
It was a good shooting.
我感觉好多了
I feel better.
跟我说真话  你为什么想当警察
Tell me the truth. Why do you wanna be a cop?
我希望我的女儿安全
I want my daughter to be safe.
为我感到骄傲
To be proud of me.
你父亲是纽瓦克的一名银行经理
Now your father, he was a bank manager in Newark.
你就跟我说说他的事情
You just tell me a little bit about him.
他在一次银行抢劫未遂中被枪杀  对吗
He was shot during an attempted robbery. Is that right?
谈话结束了
We're done.
七月一日
德兹  到主管办公室报到
Dezi? Dezi? Report to the supervisor office.
-老板    -德兹  坐下
-Boss?    -Dezi, take a seat.
有个贝斯顿银行抢劫案的目击者
I got a witness from the Beston Bank robbery
说你拒绝提供医疗救助
that says you refused to offer medical assistance.
伤员鉴别分类
Triage.
这里不是战区
This isn't a war zone.
你想让我救坏人还是救受害者
Would you rather me save the villain or the victim?
-我看过你的报告    -是的
-I read your report.    -Yes.
我们到了现场  对吧
We arrived on the scene, right?
已经看过死去的警察
We're past the dead cop.
我做出了判断  然后我们走进了经理办公室
I made a judgment call and then we went into the manager's office.
你那样抬他出来违反了规定
You broke protocol carrying him out like that.
我救了他的命
I saved the guy's life.
他正在起诉市政府和你
He's suing the city and you
在紧急运输过程中遭受的精神伤害
for emotional trauma sustained during emergency transportation.
去他妈的
Get the f--
-你被停职了    -什么
-You're suspended.    -What?
-德兹    -我没做错什么
-Dezi.    -I did nothing wrong.
休息几周
Take a few weeks.
让法律部门来解决  这事就过去了
Let legal come to a resolution, it'll blow over.
这他妈的不公平
That's not fucking fair!
你以为你能这样跟我说话
You think you can talk to me like this?
不管了
Fuck it.
你因违抗命令和拒绝
You're fired for insubordination
向有需要的人提供医疗援助而被解雇
and refusing to offer medical assistance to someone in need.
你不能解雇我
You can't fire me.
你的合同现在终止了
Your contract is terminated now.
你不能开除我
You can't fire me,
因为我是你最好的助手
'cause I'm the best fucking para you fucking got.
你炒了我  就是害了整座城市
You fire me and you hurt the whole fucking city.
大话谁不会说  滚出我的办公室
Big fucking whoop. Get out of my office.
现在  我们生活的社会
Right now, we live in a society
运行着两条不同的规则
where there's one rule for us and another rule for them.
不只是这里  全世界都是这样
That's notjust here. That's all over the world.
这种情况正在蔓延  全世界盛行
That's spreading right now. That's the pandemic.
我们不是被评判的人
We are not judged people.
富人  名人  他们所有人都有自己的秘密
The rich, the famous, all of them, they have their agenda.
他们决定什么是对  什么是错
They decide what's right and what's wrong.
但我们知道什么是正确
But we know what's right.
我们知道什么是正确
We know what's right.
你看到波特兰了吗
You see Portland?
这个世界将和波特兰一模一样
The world is gonna look exactly like Portland
如果我们没有英雄
if we don't have heroes.
世界需要英雄
The world needs heroes.
警察是世界上最辛苦的工作
Cops have the hardest job in the world.
这座城市正在分崩离析
This city is tearing itself apart
警察就是我们的最后一道防线
and cops are our last line of defense.
我们需要的警察  不在乎繁文缛节
We need cops who don't care about red tape,
不在乎政治
who don't care about the politics,
有可能成为市长或者只有四年任期
and who's gonna become mayor or a four-year term limit.
取消对警察的资助
Defund the police?
对  是的  当然  好主意
Right, yeah, sure, great idea.
取消对警察的资助  看看谁会来救援
Defund the police and then see who comes to the rescue
利益集团为所欲为
when cartels are running free,
就连你喝咖啡的时候
when you-- when you can't even get
都有可能被抢劫
a cup of coffee without getting mugged.
这是有些人如何入狱的问题
It's about how people go to jail.
你永远也看不到  警察做的那些好事
You will never see it, all the good things that the cops do.
你永远不会看到他们解决家庭暴力事件
You will never see them breaking up domestic violence incidents,
组织食物捐助活动  因为那不是好的内容
organizing, food drives, 'cause that's not good content.
取消资助  是的  好的  我可以等
Defund it, yeah. Cool, I'll wait.
布茨  过来
Hey, Boots, come here.
国庆日早上你有什么安排
What have you got going on the morning of the Fourth?
我要和我女朋友去海滩  长官
I'm headed to the beach with my girl, sir.
我已经期盼了一个星期
Been looking forward to it all week.
我们在为危险避难所寻找志愿者
We're looking for volunteers for the at-risk shelter.
布置  食物  清洁  你懂的
Setting up, you know, food, cleaning, you know.
-对    -我不能强迫你答应
-Yeah.    -I can't force you to say yes.
但我可以告诉警长你拒绝了
But I can tell the sergeant that you declined.
我很乐意去  但我们为这计划了一个月
I would love to, but we've been planning this for a month.
我得去机场接她妈妈
I got to pick her mom at the airport.
好吧  给我
Fine. Give it to me.
服务和保护
Serve and protect.
好吧  这是我应做的
Well, this is me serving.
你得保护我不受我女友的伤害
I'm gonna need you to protect me from my girlfriend.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我没开玩笑
You think I'm kidding.
谁来看守看守人
Quis custodiet ipsos custodes.
谁来监视监视者
Who watches the watcher?
有太多的人
Too many people.
警方无法在媒体和公众
Police can't effectively, do their job
如此严格的监督下有效地完成工作
with this level of scrutiny from the media and, the public.
我说警察做得不够
I say cops don't do enough.
他们需要能倾倒垃圾
They need to go-- someone that can take out the trash
而不必担心繁文缛节
and doesn't have to worry about the red tape.
我不是在说  义警  我说的是
I'm not talking about, a vigilante. I'm talking more of a...
正义天使
Angel of Justice.
义警  我说的是
...vigilante. I'm talking more of a...
正义天使
Angel of Justice. Angel of Justice.
正义天使  正义  正义
Angel of Justice. Justice... Justice...
正义  正义  正义  正义
Justice... Justice... Justice... Justice...
正义天使
Angel of Justice.
奈特  马上来我办公室
Knight! My office, now.
-嘿  老板    -闭嘴
-Hey, boss.    -Shut up.
是  长官
Yes, ma'am.
-你在做什么    -文书工作
-What are you working?    -Paperwork.
-得谢谢你    -好的
-No thanks to you.    -Good.
这里还有一些
Here's some more.
有人偷了制服  警徽  枪
Someone stole a uniform, badge, gun,
事件发生在
the whole shebang from
北路医院的验尸官办公室
the coroner's office down at North Roads Hospital.
警局想要回警徽  内务部想要回枪
Family wants the badge back, I.A. wants the gun,
我想知道什么样的堕落者才会做出这种事
and I want to know what kind of degenerate would do such a thing.
-没有安全摄像头    -没有
-No security cameras?    -Nope.
没有  出于隐私原因
No. Privacy reasons.
隐私原因
Privacy?
那个警察已经死亡
The customers are dead.
这意味着你又得去跑腿了
That means you're gonna have to do a little leg work.
从表面上看
And by the looks of things,
你可以分几个步骤做
you could do with getting in some more steps.
就像我看到的那样
Just calling it like I see it.
你晚上睡得如何
You sleeping all right?
谢谢你的注意
Thank you for noticing.
我昨晚很晚才回来
I was out late night.
缉毒组截获了几吨可卡因和几个女人
Narcotics Unit intercepted a couple of tons of coke and some women.
-贩毒集团    -他们希望如此
-Cartel shit?    -Oh, they wish.
不  是吸血鬼帮
No, it's the Vampos Gang.
我猜所有的名字都有人了
I guess all the names were-- were taken.
噢  恭喜你离婚了
Oh, hey, congrats on the divorce.
我是个自由人了
I'm a free man.
是啊  你的无名指是自由了
Yeah, well, your ring finger may be free,
但你这个人还是属于警局的
but your ass still belongs to the department.
难道我不知道
Don't I know it.
-你女儿怎么样    -她很好
-How's your daughter?    -She's fine.
我可不会用“好”这个词来形容你女儿
Fine is not the "F" word I would use to describe your daughter.
不过话说回来  她有你这样的爸爸
But then again, hey, I mean, she's got a dad like you
还有卡米拉这样的妈妈
and a mom like Camilla.
心理医生大老远就可以诊断出这些父亲的问题
A shrink could diagnose those daddy issues three states away.
有人在你的咖啡里撒尿了
Did somebody piss in your coffee?
我只是说有办法
I'm just saying that there's a way
平衡工作和家庭生活
to balance out work and home life.
你有过几个丈夫
How many husbands have you had?
听着  我没说我知道怎么平衡
Look, I-- I didn't say I knew how to balance it out,
我只是说有办法
I'm just saying there is a way.
我是说  你看菲兹
You know, I mean, look at Fitz.
-菲兹是个好人    -他被鞭策了
-Fitz is a good boy.    -He's whipped.
那倒没错
That is true.
不过他是个好警察
He's a good cop, though.
你凭什么这么说
What makes you say that?
没有比这更好的了
There's none finer.
不  我现在很好奇
No, I'm-- I'm curious now.
你认为什么是好警察
What do you think makes a good cop?
好警察睡不好觉  别人就能睡好觉
A good cop doesn't sleep well, so everyone else can.
我接受
I'll accept that.
最后一件事
Oh, one last thing.
你和菲兹四日要值班
You and Fitz are working the Fourth.
我要去露营
I'm going camping.
露营
Camping?
是啊  我有间小木屋
Yeah. I got a cabin.
那不是露营
Ah, that's not camping.
除非我有时间
Not unless I get time off.
国庆日  我最喜欢这一天
The Fourth? It's my favorite day.
我希望你们面带微笑地保护和服务人民
And I expect you to protect and serve with a smile on your face.
谢谢你  奈特
Thank you, Knight.
我们擅长经营养老金  你的未来有保障
Pensions are our specialty. Your future is safe.
我在这里开户
I bank here.
开个账户  我们可以给你一些不错的复利
Set up an account, and we can get you some nice compound interest
也许投资对你更好
or maybe an investment would be better for you.
投资账户有多少钱  好  没问题
How much do you-- investment account? Okay, that's fine.
警官  有什么事吗
Officer! What can I do for you?
-我  呃    -噢
-I, uh...    -Oh.
你是来检查的
Are you here to do a 6-8-9?
对  是的
Yes. Yeah.
加科夫斯基小姐  警官  想检查
Miss Gakowski. The officer... Oh! Wants to do a 6-8-9.
你没事吧  警官
Are you okay, Officer?
你的制服穿起来有点松垮
Your uniform looks kind of wonky.
打电话给联盟
Call the union,
警局不应该让你这样出来
the department should not be sending you out like that.
我见过你吗
Do I know you?
那晚你在这里
Were you here that night
那帮混蛋打劫我金库那晚
those tweaker assholes made a run at my vault?
是的
Yeah.
我是说  我听说过
I mean, I-- I heard about that.
我都快完蛋了  是你们救了我
My ass was almost cooked, but you boys saved my life.
我相信那些护理人员也做得很好
I'm sure those paramedics did a good job, too.
那些警察兄弟
It was the Blue Bloods,
还有圣玛丽医院的医生  他们是英雄
and the doctors at Saint Mary's, they're the heroes.
你是十四组成员
Are you part of the 14th?
我认识一个人
I have a guy whose
他父亲曾经是夜间指挥官  詹姆斯·杰恩
father used to be the Night Commander, James Jayne?
是的  当然
Oh, yeah, sure.
你认识他
You know him?
是的  好人
Yeah. Good man.
-我以为他死了    -你知道
-I thought he died.    -Well, you know...
警察永远不会死
Cops never die.
阿门  兄弟  警察生命永不消逝
Amen, brother. Blue lives never die.
谢谢你们所做的一切
Thank you for what you do.
你国庆节有什么计划
So do you have any plans for the Fourth?
还是老样子
You know, the usual.
好啦好啦  工作不息
Now, now, work never ceases.
我能理解  我会在这里埋头苦干
I can relate. I will be here toiling away.
但我很喜欢
But I love it.
在国庆日赚钱更具有美国特色
There's nothing more American, than making money on the Fourth.
上帝啊  进来吧
Jesus Christ! Come on in.
在这边
Have at it.
是的
Yeah.
我们被撤资了
We've been defunded.
我用尽了所有力气才让这里的灯亮着
Takes all my strength to keep the lights on here.
快  快  快
Go, go, go.
趴下
Get down!
趴在地上
Get on the ground!
趴下
Get down!
你  马上打开收银台
You, open the register right now!
等一下
Wait, hang on...
快走  快走  我们走
Let's go, let's go! Come on, let's go!
不  快做  我们走
No, fucking do it. Come on, let's go!
打开收银台
Open the register!
打开金库  快去
Fucking vault's open, let's go for it.
趴下
Stay down!
趴在地上  你  面靠墙
Let's go. Stay on the ground. You, against the wall!
低下头
Get your head down!
趴在地上别动
Let's go, stay on the fucking ground.
你没事吧
You all right?
我说不要去金库
I said no vault!
看看这些该死的现金
Look at all the fucking cash!
我他妈的中枪了
I'm fucking shot, dude.
那就他妈快点帮帮我
Well, then hurry the fuck up and help me.
去你的  贪心的混蛋  快拿钱
Fuck you! You greedy fuck, get the money!
你他妈想快点离开  就去拿钱
You wanna fucking get out of here, get the fucking money.
操
Fuck!
别乱动  别拿手机  都不许动
Don't fucking move. No cell phones, nothing. Nobody move.
我会听话的  谢谢
I'll take that. Thank you very much.
快走  你这个胆小鬼
Fucking let's go, you crybaby!
操  快点
Fuck! Fuck! In a minute!
趴下
Stay down.
这个庇护所  是一种遗产
This shelter, it's a legacy.
只要保持开放  传承就会持续下去
As long as it stays open, her memory will last.
一切正常
All clear.
好人
Good man.
警官  求你了  你得帮帮我
Officer! Officer, please, you have to help me!
你得帮帮我
You have to help me.
你得帮我  求你了  我的丈夫
You have to help me. Please, my husband. He's--
-不  我不是    -警官
-No, I'm not a--    -Officer!
不  我不当班
No, I'm off duty.
什么  你算什么警察
What? What kind of cop are you?
好吧  我需要你冷静下来
Okay, I need you to-- I need you to calm down.
听着  我要你冷静点
Okay, look, I need you to calm down. Okay?
-他在哪    -他在这儿
-Where is he?    -He's over here.
他在这里  他们在那边
He's here. He's over here. They're over there.
在这里
Over here.
你这弱鸡
And you're weak.
举起手来
Hands up!
举起手
Yeah, hands!
走  离开这里
Go. Get out of here!
把手放在墙上
Hands against the wall.
快点
Now!
好了
All right.
把腿分开
Now spread 'em.
好了  现在你们都
All right, now you all...
有权利
have the right...
保持沉默
to remain silent.
任何东西
And anything...
这是什么
What's this?
这个
This!
都会成为证据
...you say will be used against you
呈上法庭
... in a court of law.
-就这样    -就这样  揍他
-That's it.    -That's it, kick his ass.
不
No.
No, no.
哎
All right.
噢  不
Oh, no!
这就是你们不尊重别人的后果
Oh! This is what happens when you do not show respect.
我是执法人员
I am an officer of the law!
好了  都跪下
Okay, get on your knees.
跪下来  面对地
Get on your knees and kiss the ground!
面对地
Kiss the ground.
贴地
Kiss it!
遵守规定  就能活下来
Comply and you'll survive.
不
No.
回答我这个问题
I mean, answer me this.
你们认为
You guys think
没有你们世界会
the world would be a better place
变得更好吗
without you in it? Huh?
-你会怎么做    -不要
-I mean, what do you do?    -No, man.
让这个国家比昨天更好
Make this country better than it was yesterday.
我这里有你的答案
I got your answer right here.
如果遵守规定  他们就会活着
If they have had complied, they would have been alive.
嘿
Hello?
谁啊
Who is it?
你不知道我今天有多惨
You won't believe the day I fucking had.
怎么了
What happened?
有个家伙在范奈斯假装警察枪杀了四个人
Some guy dressed up as a cop shot four guys in Van Nuys.
全部死亡
No one made it.
他们找到枪手了
Did they find the shooter?
还没有  不过会的
Not yet. But they will.
那个家伙假装成警察
I mean, guy was dressed up as a cop,
一副要逮捕他们的样子
acting like he was gonna arrest them.
警方对他的动机一无所知
The police don't know shit about his motive.
该死
Damn.
这很不好
It isn't fair.
也许这能让警察保持紧张
Well, maybe it'll keep the cops on their toes.
稍微改变一下
Shake things up a bit.
别这样说
Don't say that, man.
为什么
Why?
你觉得警察会在乎我们
Oh, you think they care about us?
儿子为父亲的罪行付出代价  一如往昔
The sons pay for the sins of their fathers. Nothing's changed.
我父亲教过我这一点
Okay? My father taught me that.
有一天我告诉他  我想当警察
I remember the day that I told him I wanted to be a cop,
他狠狠地打了我一拳
and he gave me the biggest backhand of my life
把我打倒在地
and knocked me down on the floor.
他说警察是我们的敌人
Told me the cops are our enemies.
还说  他们都是猪
And, you know, they're just pigs...
是起诉逃亡奴隶的奴隶主的后代
descended from slave owners who prosecuted runaway slaves.
独立战争  只不过为了国家的税收
Like, the War of Independence, that's for this country's taxes,
美国内战
and the American Civil War,
虽然他们解放了奴隶
well, that's like, you know, they freed the slaves,
但没有人真正自由  我们没有自由
but no one's really free. We're not free.
我们永远不会自由
We'll never be free.
不管我们是谁
Doesn't matter who we are,
他们都会卖给我们同样的美国梦
they'll sell us the same fucking American dream.
这很可悲  太可悲了  不过
And it's sad. It's so sad. It's just...
那些有钱人就像肖恩·贝斯顿
It's about money and guys like, what, Sean Beston.
他就是  他就是个奴隶主
You know, he's-- he's just a-- he's a slave owner.
而那些警察
And the cops?
就是他的打手
His goons.
我很抱歉你有这种感觉
I'm sorry you feel that way.
事实就是如此
Yeah. It is what it is.
我以为我终于可以释怀
I thought I got over this for once.
再见
See you.
文尼  他妈的钱呢
Vinny, where's the fucking money?
这家伙是谁  他是个警察
Who's this guy? You know he's a fucking cop.
我儿子不是警察
No son of mine's a cop.
儿子  你他妈穿这个干什么
What the fuck you wearing, son?
制服造就不了真男人
It's not the uniform that makes the man.
运气只能靠自己创造
The man that makes his own luck.
别用我的话来反驳我
Don't throw my fucking words back in my face.
万圣节要等明年十月  那时你就可以装扮一下
Halloween is next October. You can dress up then.
你想帮忙
You want to help?
就帮忙煮饭
Start with meal prep.
我们可以改变世界
We can change the world.
我是说警察
I mean cops.
他们每天都把孩子关起来  但这个呢
They lock up kids every day, but this?
这是事实
This is real.
这个庇护所可以防止孩子变成这两样人
This shelter stops kids from becoming these two.
这是我们的机会
This is our chance.
还有多久  这里的灯就会永远熄灭
How long before the, the lights go out in this place for good?
有志者事竟成
Where there's a will, there's a way.
我说的是实际行动
I'm talking about real action.
一种真正的改变方式
You know, a real way to make change.
也许你的新同事可以帮忙
Maybe your new associates can help.
继续说
Go on.
-贝斯顿信托银行    -怎么了
-Beston Bank and Trust.    -What about it?
安全系统  无处不在
Its security system, it's all over the place.
但那些警卫  他们很自大
The guards, they're arrogant, like...
我可以带我们进去
I can get us in.
所以呢
So?
我们抢劫
We hit it.
看看外面世界  有没有看到美国梦
When you look outside, I mean, do you see the American dream?
或者看到别人的
Or do you see someone else's?
尴尬城市  然后赚点奶酪
Embarrass the city, and make some cheese?
我操
I can fuck with that.
在我们生活的社会里  没有什么比
We live in a society where there is nothing more American
在国庆日赚钱更具有美国特色
than making money on the 4th of July.
七月四日
凯西·罗兹应该在监狱里等死
Casey Rhodes should be rotting in jail.
你就不能肯定一次
Could you be positive for once?
我是活力的源泉  奈特兄弟
Hey, I'm a fountain of good vibes, brother Knight.
阿呆与阿瓜
If it isn't dumb and dumber,
摩登原始人
Barney Rubble and... this caveman.
他叫什么来着
What's his name again?
你竟然忘了弗雷德的名字
Can't believe you forgot Fred's name.
我们在执行软任务
Anyway, we're on soft duty.
不是吧
That isn't real.
软任务是比硬任务高一杯啤酒
Soft duty is one beer above hard duty
比我们的狂欢低三杯
and three below let's party.
他妈的真堕落
Fucking degenerates.
你们其中一个应该进监狱  另一个应该坐椅子
One of you should be in jail and the other in the chair.
你有什么毛病
Have you got a problem?
我就这样说  你想怎么样
If I did, what would you do?
-国庆日快乐    -是啊
-Happy Fourth.    -Yeah.
谢谢你  笨蛋
Thank you, douchebags.
倒霉  我在车里等你
Shit! I'll meet you in the car.
好了  开始吧
All right, let's do this.
准备好了
You ready?
幸运的混蛋
You lucky son of a bitch.
这一次我宁愿继续坐在椅子上
The one time I'd rather still be in the chair.
嘿
Hey!
你们知道你们会在监狱里度过余生
You guys know you're going to jail for the rest of your lives.
对吧
Right?
我只是开玩笑
Fine, I'm just playing.
你们在这里干什么
All right, what do you got here?
这是罗马焰火筒
Is that a Roman candle?
让我看看这东西  如果你们
Let me see that thing. Listen, if you guys...
要把这些都点燃
are gonna light these off,
你们要注意安全
you gotta be safe about it.
因为这些东西可以造成真正的伤害
Because you could do some real damage with one of these things.
明白吗  要把焰火指向空中
You understand? I want you to point 'em in the air.
不能对着人  也不能对着动物或狗  明白吗
Not at people, not at animals, not at dogs. You understand?
如果我看到用这个指着狗
If I see you pointing this at a dog,
我会当着你奶奶的面踩你
I'm gonna curb stomp you in front of your grandmother.
你们明白吗
Do you understand?
很好
All right, good.
是的
Yes?
你和她谈过了吗
Did you speak with her?
只要她想和你谈谈  她会主动联系你
She will reach out whenever she's ready to talk to you.
我只是想确定她没事
Just want to make sure that she's okay.
请告诉我她住在哪里
Please tell me where she's living.
她有男朋友了
She got a boyfriend. I--
什么  谁
What? Who?
噢  现在像个超级老爹
Oh, don't go all super dad now.
现在不行  何时
If not now, when?
那个新人怎么样
How's the new guy?
你没资格问这样的问题
You don't get to ask questions like that.
我只是随便问问
I'm just saying.
你开心就好
You can do better.
如果他对你好  我会支持的
If he treats you right, I'll support that.
我只想让你和我们的女儿
All I want is for you and our girl
平安快乐
to be happy and safe.
就这样
That's all.
你觉得我们本来有可能一起做好
Do you think we, could have, ever worked?
你把工作放在第一位  我没有责怪你  没有
You put the job first and I'm not blaming you, I'm not.
只有几个小时  这样没法一起过日子
Just the hours. It was no way to raise a family.
我们就像船只在黑夜中穿行
We were like, ships passing through the night.
是啊
Yeah.
我们要找的是一样的  一样的冰山
Yeah, we're going for the same, yeah, the same iceberg.
你把小熊给她了吗
Hey, did you give her the bear?
我见到她  我会交给她
When I see her, I will.
国庆日快乐  警探
Happy Fourth, Detective.
-嘿  宝贝    -嗨
-Hey, honey.    -Hi.
你爸爸一直在找你
Dad's been trying to get ahold of you.
为什么
Why?
他是你爸爸
He's your father.
爸爸偶尔
And fathers do care about
也会关心孩子的健康
the well-being of their children, occasionally.
他很抱歉错过了你的生日
He's sorry he missed your birthday.
是啊  这个跟去年给我买的一模一样
Yeah, and didn't he get me this exact same one last year?
-你是他的小公主    -随便
-You're his little princess.    -Whatever.
谢谢
Thank you.
-呃哼    -好的  噢
-Ahem.    -Okay. Oh, ooh.
你爸爸把你当小孩
You are your father's child.
你现在高兴了
You happy now?
再来三只小熊  我会
Yeah. Three more of those and I will be.
还有
And...
你的制服也很漂亮
And nice of you to dress up, too.
我随叫随到
I'm on call.
想喝酒吗
Wanna do shots?
不  这些是迈克工作上的朋友
No. These are Mike's work friends.
是的
Oh, yeah.
我们可不想让他难堪
We wouldn't want to embarrass him.
做个问题小孩
To being a problem child.
噢不  敬好父母
Oh, no. To good parenting.
噢
Oh.
你干嘛逼我这样做
Oh. Why did you make me do that?
-太好了  耶    -不
-That's so good. Yeah.    -No. No.
来  妈妈  耶
Go, mom. Go, mom. Yeah!
-国庆日快乐  警官    -的确
-Happy Fourth, Officer, happy Fourth.    -Indeed.
有什么事吗
What can I do for you?
我来这里检查
I'm here to do a 6-8-9.
我们这里完全没问题
Well, we've never been better.
我
Well, I...
我只是来检查一下你的情况
I'm just here to check up on you, sir.
你真是太好了  不过一切都好  一切都很好
Well, that's very kind of you, but all is well. All is well.
如果让我进去  你就帮了我一个忙
You'd be doing me a favor if you let me inside,
我就可以亲眼看看了
so I can see for myself.
你在干什么  噢  你
What are you doing? Oh, you!
后面还有两个  混蛋
Hey, there's two back there! Fucker--
你想让我进去
You want to let me inside?
退后  你们这些王八蛋
Stay back! Stay back, you motherfuckers!
-扔掉枪    -退后
-Drop it, drop it.    -Get back!
-放下武器    -退后
-Put your weapons down!    -Back! Get the...
开门  打开门
Open it up. Open up! Open it up!
我即将实现我的美国梦
I am about to live my American dream.
贝斯顿先生  请留在原地
Mr. Beston, please stay where you are.
警卫  放下枪  你们可以走了
Guards, put down your guns. You're free to go.
他妈的烦
Fuck it!
噢
Oh!
来吧
Come on.
你他妈的疯了
You're fucking crazy.
你还记得我吗
Do you remember me?
说我是谁
Tell me who I am.
Tell me who I am!
还不说
Still don't?
调度中心  所有单位到贝斯顿银行
911, all units to Beston Bank.
可能发生银行抢劫
Possible 211 in progress.
回家  好好做功课
Get home. Do some homework.
双骑士117
2 Knight 117.
四分钟
Four minutes out.
阿尔瓦拉多
Alvarado.
吓坏了那些小混蛋
Scared the little bastards.
太老了  不适合干这破事
Too old for this shit.
所有单位
All units, all units.
贝斯顿信托银行发生抢劫
Robbery in progress at Beston Bank and Trust.
据说  嫌疑人全副武装
Suspects are reportedly heavily armed.
-完毕    -完毕
-Set?    -Set.
准备出发
Lock and load.
来吧  小伙子
Here we go, boys.
好了
Bingo!
尼科  快去看
Nico, check that out!
小家伙  你来照顾我们的新朋友
Hey, boy scout, why don't you take care of our new friend?
是的  我现在刚到地点
Yeah, I just got to the location now.
一切看起来都很正常
Everything looks pretty normal.
-嘿  各位    -天哪  似曾相识
-Hey, gentlemen!    -Christ, I'm having déjà vu.
目击者说有三个人进入了这里
Witnesses said they saw three guys go in here.
其中一人打扮成警察
One was dressed as a cop.
我们到底要不要进去
We going in or what?
该死  找掩护
Oh, shit! Take cover.
是的  有人开枪了  枪击
Yeah, shots fired. Shots fired. Shots fired.
马上把你的车开过来  枪击
Need your fucking cars right now! Shots fired!
嘿  蹲下
Hey, get down!
帮忙  警官中枪
Help! Officer down!
小心  看看这个
Watch. Check this out.
奈特
Knight!
你开枪打屋顶
You shoot the roof.
继续
Keep going.
装弹  掩护我
Reloading. Cover me!
震爆弹在哪里
Where's the stun grenade?
警察在门口  快走
Cops are at the door, let's go.
妈的  快走  操
Shit! Let's go! Fuck it, man.
来吧  你能行的  没问题
Come on, D. You got it, mate. You got it.
-帮我    -警察都中枪
-Help me!    -Fucking officer down!
这里没有人
I can't see dick in here.
见鬼
Shit.
他们在哪里
Where the fuck are they?
好了  派个人去屋顶
All right, someone take the roof.
行动  快点
Move! Let's go!
滚出去  趴在地上  否则  我就射你
Fuck out! Down on the ground! Otherwise, I'll fuck you.
检查出口
Check the exit.
来吧
Come on!
不  把枪放下
No. Drop the gun down.
艾丽  你冷静点
Ally. Ally, you have to calm down.
不  我得进去
No, I have to go in.
你会安全的  你会没事的
You'll be safe, you'll be fine.
走吧
Let's go.
完美  爱死这个了  好
Perfect. Fucking love it. Yes!
-那些混蛋    -艾丽
-Those fuckers!    -Ally...
什么意思  她怎么了
What do you mean? What about her?
快走
Let's go.
该死  这可不是好事
Oh, shit. This isn't gonna be good.
嫌犯偷了一辆耶稣会救护车
Suspect has stolen a Jesuit Medical ambulance,
在帝国大道上向南行驶
heading southbound on Imperial Highway.
他们有人质  重复  他们有人质
They have a hostage. I repeat, they have a hostage.
艾丽  没事  拜托  请冷静
Ally, it's fine. Just please, calm down, please.
什么  不  这是怎么回事
What? No, what is happening?
那两个是什么人
Who are those two guys?
请冷静点
Please just calm down.
德兹  有人来了
Hey, Dezi, we've got incoming.
我们往山上走  在峡谷里会甩掉他们
Let's head for the hills, we'll lose them in the canyons.
操  这该死的救护车
Fuck this! This fucking ambulance.
他妈最慢的救护车  快点  宝贝
Slowest fucking ambulance! Come on, baby.
拜托  快点
Come on! Come on! Come on!
奈特  关上该死的门
Knight, close the goddamn door!
回来关上门  你这样射击可能害了艾丽
Get out and close the door. You can hit Ally with that aim.
你在哪里学的开车
Where did you learn to drive?
你  等一下
You. Now hold on.
他们就跟在我们后面  快想办法
They're right on us, mate! Do something.
好的
Right.
干掉他  德兹  干掉他
Fucking kill him, Dezi, kill him!
见鬼
Holy shit!
我们正在接近他们
We are coming up on them now.
搞什么鬼
What the fuck?
拜托  宝贝  快点
Come on, baby. Come on! Come on!
-有没有听到    -听到什么
-Hey, do you hear that?    -Hear what, you fuck?
该死  看  狗仔队  狗仔队
Oh, shit! Look, paparazzi! Paparazzi!
狗仔队  蓝色狗仔队
Paparazzi... Blue paparazzi.
我们出名了  尼科  出名了
We're gonna be famous, Nico. Famous!
兄弟  那不是娱乐新闻网
Hey, bro, that ain't TMZ. That ain't TMZ, bro.
向后摆动
Swinging back around.
我射击后驾驶室
And I'm shooting the back cab.
射死他们  尼科  干掉警察回来
Shoot 'em! Nico, get the fucking cops and get in!
-射杀他们    -快他妈开枪
-I can shoot 'em.    -Just fucking shoot him, mate.
操  这可是侠盗猎车手的大事  兄弟
Fuck, this is some serious GTA shit, bruv!
绕回去  绕回去  绕回去
Come back around. Go back around. Go back around.
我是怎么说那扇门的
What did I say about that door?
干掉他们  尼科  开枪  开枪
Get 'em, Nico, shoot, shoot, shoot!
他妈的开枪
Fucking shoot this fuck!
操  尼科  你没事  过来
Oh, fuck, Nico. You all right, come here.
尼科
Nico!
该死
Shit!
保持稳定
Keep it steady.
那个小混蛋打到轮胎了
That little shit hit the tire.
趁他重新装弹我们有机会  开稳点
Now is our chance while he reloads. Keep it steady.
妈的  快点  轮胎不行了
Shit! Hurry up! This tire's fading fast.
我开稳点  快去救你女儿
I got you. Now, go get your daughter.
德兹  德兹
Dezi! Dezi!
抓住那个老混蛋
Hold that old fucker in there!
王八蛋
Motherfucker.
别这样  老头
Don't do it, old man.
哟  你没事吧  天哪
Yo, yo, you all right? Holy shit!
退后  退后
Get back, get back.
Stay back. Stay back.
退后
Stay back!
退后  王八蛋  我宰了你们
Stay back, you motherfuckers! I'll kill all of you.
好了  掩护现场  绕到后面去  快
All right, cover the field! Just go around back! Quick!
爸爸
Dad!
爸爸  真他妈越来越好玩了
Dad? Oh, this keeps getting fucking better.
扔掉枪
Drop the fucking gun!
开枪打这个该死的混蛋
Shoot this fucking asshole.
不
No.
放开她
Let her go.
我说放开她
I said, let her go.
事情不应该是这样的
It wasn't supposed to be like this!
我为这个国家付出了我的一切
I gave everything I had to this country.
我试着循规蹈矩  结果你看我落得什么下场
I tried playing by the rules and look where it fucking got me.
你认为呢
You think?
你认为我是坏人  那你就是被洗脑了
You're brainwashed if you think I'm the bad guy.
他们付我钱不是让我来审判
They don't pay me to judge.
不  你只是个带着警徽的杀手
No. You're just a sicario with a badge.
他们叫你开枪  你就开枪
You shoot anyone they tell you to.
政府
The government?
政府  政府就是城里最大的帮派
The government-- the government is the biggest gang in town.
把枪放下
Put the gun down.
我会成为这座城市有史以来最好的警察
I would have been the best cop this city has ever had.
你没有权利穿那身制服
You got no right to wear that uniform.
警徽  这不代表他是个男人
The badge, it doesn't... It doesn't make the man.
你认为我当不了好警察
You don't think I could have been a good cop,
就算我他妈的有机会
if I just had a fucking chance?
当个混蛋是没药可治的
There's no cure for being an asshole.
我只想做个好人
All I wanted was to be the good guy.
就这样
That's it.
我们按发的牌来打
We play the cards we're dealt.
有时我们会赢
Sometimes we win.
有时我们会咬人
And sometimes we bite.
你大爷的
Fuck you.
-艾丽  艾丽    -我了解
-Ally! Ally!    -I got you.
求你了  告诉他们我是个好人
Please, tell them I'm a good guy. Tell them.
艾丽
Ally!
没关系
It's okay.
我不会开枪  我是好人
I'm not gonna shoot, I'm the good guy.
我是好人  我是好人
I'm the good guy. I'm the good...
国庆日快乐  王八蛋
Happy Fourth, motherfucker!